const level5Questions = [
 {
        question: "Xin hỏi",
        answers: ["请问 (qǐng wèn)", "问 (wèn)"],
        correct: "请问 (qǐng wèn)",
    },
    {
        question: "Họ",
        answers: ["贵姓 (guìxìng)", "姓 (xìng)"],
        correct: "姓 (xìng)",
    },
    {
        question: "Gọi",
        answers: ["叫 (jiào)", "名字 (míngzi)"],
        correct: "叫 (jiào)",
    },
    {
        question: "Nước, quốc gia",
        answers: ["哪 (nǎ)", "国 (guó)"],
        correct: "国 (guó)",
    },
    {
        question: "Nước Đức",
        answers: ["中国 (Zhōngguó)", "德国 (Déguó)"],
        correct: "德国 (Déguó)",
    },
    {
        question: "Nước Pháp",
        answers: ["俄国 (Éguó)", "法国 (Fǎguó)"],
        correct: "法国 (Fǎguó)",
    },
    {
        question: "Giáo sư",
        answers: ["教授 (jiàoshòu)", "校长 (xiàozhǎng)"],
        correct: "教授 (jiàoshòu)",
    },
    {
        question: "Hàn Quốc",
        answers: ["韩国 (Hánguó)", "日本 (Rìběn)"],
        correct: "韩国 (Hánguó)",
    },
    {
        question: "Nhật Bản",
        answers: ["日本 (Rìběn)", "英国 (Yīngguó)"],
        correct: "日本 (Rìběn)",
    },
    {
        question: "Nó",
        answers: ["人 (rén)", "它 (tā)"],
        correct: "它 (tā)",
    },
    {
        question: "Chữ Hán",
        answers: ["学习 (xuéxí)", "汉字 (Hànzì)"],
        correct: "汉字 (Hànzì)",
    },
    {
        question: "Cái gì, gì",
        answers: ["什么 (shénme)", "书 (shū)"],
        correct: "什么 (shénme)",
    },
    {
        question: "Phát âm",
        answers: ["发音 (fāyīn)", "什么 (shénme)"],
        correct: "发音 (fāyīn)",
    },
    {
        question: "Ai",
        answers: ["谁 (shéi / shuí)", "的 (de)"],
        correct: "谁 (shéi / shuí)",
    },
    {
        question: "Tạp chí",
        answers: ["那 (nà)", "杂志 (zázhì)"],
        correct: "杂志 (zázhì)",
    },
    {
        question: "Giáo sư",
        answers: ["教授 (jiàoshòu)", "校长 (xiàozhǎng)"],
        correct: "教授 (jiàoshòu)",
    },
];

export default level5Questions;
